<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content>
  
  <item name="DbEntryComparison">
    <para>
      The <see cref="KeggId"/> returned by this method in derived classes actually boxes a more specific, derived <see cref="KeggId"/>.  
      For example, <see cref="ModuleDb"/>'s <see cref="ModuleDb.Entry(uint)"/> method returns a <see cref="MNumber"/> boxed as a <see cref="KeggId"/>,
      while <see cref="DiseaseDb"/>'s <see cref="DiseaseDb.Entry(uint)"/> method returns a <see cref="HNumber"/> boxed as a <see cref="KeggId"/>.
    </para>
    <para>
      In addition, most derived database classes also expose a method for fetching strongly typed database entries.
      For example, <see cref="ModuleDb"/> has a <see cref="ModuleDb.Module(uint)"/> method for fetching <see cref="MNumber"/> entries,
      while <see cref="DiseaseDb"/> has a <see cref="DiseaseDb.Disease(uint)"/> method for fetching <see cref="HNumber"/> entries.
      Thus, the following two method calls return an identical object; the latter is simply more specific (and more readable) than the former.
    </para>
    <code language="cs" title="Comparison of Database Entry Query Methods" source="Databases/DbEntryComparison.cs" region="Inline Code"></code>
    <para>
      The strongly typed methods should always be preferred for fetching database entries; its use is both more readable and less error prone.  
      This <see langword="abstract"/> method should only be used in rare situations where you need to look up a specific database entry by ID number, 
      but do not have access to the strongly typed database instance.
    </para>
  </item>
  <item name="CompoundVsComposite">
    <note type="caution">Do not confuse a KEGG "composite" database with the <token>CompoundDbLink</token> database.  
    A composite database is a database that is "composed of" several "simple" KEGG databases.  For example, the <token>LigandDbLink</token> 
    composite database includes data from the <token>ReactionDbLink</token>, <token>ReactionClassDbLink</token>, and <token>GlycanDbLink</token> databases, among others.  
    The <token>CompoundDbLink</token> database, on the other hand, is a particular simple database, which contains data on chemical compounds.
  </note>
  </item>

  <item name="GenomeDbEntryComments">
    <summary>
      Returns the <token>GenomeDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>GenomeDbPrefix</token> number.
    </summary>
    <param name="number">
      The <token>GenomeDbPrefix</token> number of the <token>GenomeDbLink</token> database entry.
    </param>
    <returns>
      A lightweight object representing the <token>GenomeDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>GenomeDbPrefix</token> number.
    </returns>
  </item>
  <item name="ReactionDbEntryComments">
    <summary>
      Returns the <token>ReactionDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>ReactionDbPrefix</token> number.
    </summary>
    <param name="number">
      The <token>ReactionDbPrefix</token> number of the <token>ReactionDbLink</token> database entry.
    </param>
    <returns>
      A lightweight object representing the <token>ReactionDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>ReactionDbPrefix</token> number.
    </returns>
  </item>
  <item name="ReactionClassDbEntryComments">
    <summary>
      Returns the <token>ReactionClassDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>ReactionClassDbPrefix</token> number.
    </summary>
    <param name="number">
      The <token>ReactionClassDbPrefix</token> number of the <token>ReactionClassDbLink</token> database entry.
    </param>
    <returns>
      A lightweight object representing the <token>ReactionClassDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>ReactionClassDbPrefix</token> number.
    </returns>
  </item>
  <item name="GlycanDbEntryComments">
    <summary>
      Returns the <token>GlycanDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>GlycanDbPrefix</token> number.
    </summary>
    <param name="number">
      The <token>GlycanDbPrefix</token> number of the <token>GlycanDbLink</token> database entry.
    </param>
    <returns>
      A lightweight object representing the <token>GlycanDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>GlycanDbPrefix</token> number.
    </returns>
  </item>
  <item name="CompoundDbEntryComments">
    <summary>
      Returns the <token>CompoundDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>CompoundDbPrefix</token> number.
    </summary>
    <param name="number">
      The <token>CompoundDbPrefix</token> number of the <token>CompoundDbLink</token> database entry.
    </param>
    <returns>
      A lightweight object representing the <token>CompoundDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>CompoundDbPrefix</token> number.
    </returns>
  </item>
  <item name="OrthologyDbEntryComments">
    <summary>
      Returns the <token>OrthologyDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>OrthologyDbPrefix</token> number.
    </summary>
    <param name="number">
      The <token>OrthologyDbPrefix</token> number of the <token>OrthologyDbLink</token> database entry.
    </param>
    <returns>
      A lightweight object representing the <token>OrthologyDbLink</token> database entry with the given <token>OrthologyDbPrefix</token> number.
    </returns>
  </item>
  <item name="EnzymeDbEntryComments">
    <summary>
      Returns the <token>EnzymeDbLink</token> database entry with the given EC number.
    </summary>
    <param name="ecClass">
      The first part of the <token>EnzymeDbLink</token> database entry's EC number, which identifies the enzyme's general catalytic role.
    </param>
    <param name="id2">
      The second part of the <token>EnzymeDbLink</token> database entry's EC number.
    </param>
    <param name="id3">
      The third part of the <token>EnzymeDbLink</token> database entry's EC number.
    </param>
    <param name="serialId">
      The fourth part of the <token>EnzymeDbLink</token> database entry's EC number, which uniquely identifies the enzyme.
    </param>
    <returns>
      A lightweight object representing the <token>EnzymeDbLink</token> database entry with the given EC number.
    </returns>
    <remarks>
      <token>ECNumberRemarks</token>
    </remarks>
  </item>

</content>
